几乎所有电动机都与变速箱一起使用。原因是这个
Almost all electric motors are used in conjunction with gearboxes. The reason for this is the
电动机产生相对低的扭矩。他们不是特别强大。但是，他们是
electric motors produce relatively low torque. They not particularly strong. However, they are
能够非常快速地旋转。因此我们可以使用变速箱来换取速度
capable of rotating very very quickly. So we can use a gearbox to trade off speed for
扭矩。当然，没有免费午餐和变速箱介绍一些东西
torque. Of course, there is no such thing as a free lunch and a gearbox introduces some
效率低下，有一些权力损失。功率损失是在热量和声学噪声方面。
inefficiency, there is some loss of power. That power lost is in terms of heat and acoustic noise.
如果你使用自行车，你可能对传动装置的概念非常熟悉。电动机
If you use a bicycle you are probably quite familiar with the concept of gearing. Electric motors
能够非常快速地旋转，但它们不会产生很大的扭矩，它们有点弱。
are capable of spinning very very quickly but they don't produce very much torque they are kind of weak.
现在有点像骑自行车上坡的问题。你想要权衡
Now it's a bit like the problem of riding your bicycle uphill. You want to trade off
大量的踏板旋转，以减少你的负荷
a large number of rotations of the pedals in order to reduce the load that you have
施加在那些踏板上。你需要以很大的速度换取大量的扭矩。
to exert on those pedals. You are trading off a lot of speed for a large amount of torque.
对于电动机来说，它与自行车是一样的，你有一个小的链轮
For an electric motor it's the same thing and as with the bicycle you have a small sprocket
在踏板的前部，后轮上有一个更大的链轮。因此对于
at the front on the pedals, and you have a larger sprocket on the back wheel. So for
电动机的每次旋转，我们只有输出轴的半个旋转
every rotation of the electric motor, we only have half a rotation of the output shaft of
电机的变速箱。因此电机旋转很快，输出轴旋转
the motor's gearbox. So the motor is spinning quite quickly, the output shaft is rotating
相当缓慢，但电机的扭矩被齿轮比放大。
rather slowly but the torque of the motor is amplified by the gear ratio.
这里我们有一台带单级减速箱的电机。我们称之为减速箱因为
Here we have a motor with a single stage reduction gearbox. We call it a reduction gearbox because
对于电机的每次旋转，输出轴旋转不到一次。当我们提到
for every rotation of the motor, the output shaft rotates less than once. When we refer
在齿轮箱的两侧，我们称之为下标所示的电机侧
to the two sides of the gearbox we refer to as the motor side which indicated by the subscript
M和负载侧表示下标L.齿轮箱的比率是大写G和
M and the load side indicated the subscript L. The ratio of the gearbox is capital G and
这就是大轮上的牙齿数量与小牙齿数量之比
that's the ratio of the number teeth on the big wheel to the number teeth on the little
轮。对于减速齿轮箱，G大于1。
wheel. And for a reduction gearbox G is greater than one.
输出转速欧米茄L在G倍欧米茄N上等于1.因此输出轴转速
The output speed omega L is equal to 1 on G times omega N. So the output shaft speed
低于电机速度。输出转矩tauL等于电动机的G倍
is lower than the motor speed. The output torque tau L is equal to G times the motor
扭矩tauM因此输出扭矩大于电机扭矩。这些都是根本
torque tau M so the output torque is greater than the motor torque. These are the fundamental
描述变速箱特性的方程式。它降低了速度和它
equations that describe the characteristics of a gearbox. It reduces the speed and it
增加扭矩。
increases the torque.